Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune are we;
水金地火木土天海です
We are known as the Solar System
わたしたち 太陽系と申します
Yes, we’re Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, and Neptune;
水金地火木土天海だよっ！
If you learn this for us, we’d be so happy!
覚えてくれたら 嬉しいな
Mercury, the water planet, small and fair,
水星マ — キュリ —  ちっちゃくて色白
But it has some big craters!
大きなクレ — タ — あるけど
They’re actually liquid; I’m a little wonder!
実は液体です 不思議ちゃん...！
Venus, the metal planet, with a temperature close to 500 degrees
金星ビ — ナス 500度近い気温
It’s moody with its waxing and waning
満ち欠けしちゃう気分屋さん
And you can see its rotation is reverse of everyone else’s!
ほら自転がみんなと逆...！
Earth, our planet, a planet full of water
地球ア — ス 水の惑星です
A miraculous star where there are living creatures
生き物がいる奇跡の星
There’s plenty of moisture on its shiny skin!
お肌つやつや 潤いたっぷり...！
Mars, the fire planet, a bright red and rowdy young fellow it is
火星マ — ズ 真っ赤な暴れん坊
Phobos and Deimos are its two moons
ファボスダイモス衛星二つ
Is it really true that there used to be water there, too?
昔は水もあったってホント？
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune are we;
水金地火木土天海です
We are known as the Solar System
わたしたち 太陽系と申します
Yes, we’re Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, and Neptune;
水金地火木土天海だよっ！
Keep on following! Are you ready?
まだまだ続くよ！ ア — ユ — レディ？
Saturn, the earthen planet, it’s really super light
土星サタ — ン すごくすっごく軽い
There’s a big ol’ hula-hoop around its stomach
お腹におっきなフラフ — プ
All around the galaxy, they totally adore it!
銀河でくるくる 憧れちゃう...！
Uranus, the heavenly king planet, with its pale shine,
天王星ウラヌス 青白い輝き
A ball rolling around the sun
太陽の周りでごろりん
Spinning like it’s rolling over!
転がるように 回ってる...！
Pluto, the dark king planet, an entity riddled with secrets
冥王星プル — ト 秘密だらけの存在
It’s not part of the solar system any more…
今はもう太陽系じゃないの...
But from here on out, it’ll be off on its own!
でもこれからも離れちゃヤだよ...！
Neptune, the sea king planet, a beautiful cobalt blue,
海王星ネプチュ — ン 綺麗なコバルトブル —
Its surface temperature is -200 degrees Celsius
表面温度摂氏マイナス200
Is it shivering again today?
今日もぶるぶる震えてる？
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune are they;
水金地火木土天海です
We are known as the Solar System
わたしたち 太陽系と申します
Yes, we’re Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, and Neptune;
水金地火木土天海だよっ！
If you learn this for us, we’d be so happy!
覚えてくれたら 嬉しいな
Me? Well, I am...
わたし？わたしのことは...
try and figure it out
調べてみてね
Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, Neptune are they;
水金地火木土天海です
We are known as the Solar System
わたしたち 太陽系と申します
Yes, we’re Mercury, Venus, Earth, Mars, Jupiter, Saturn, Uranus, and Neptune;
水金地火木土天海だよっ！
If you learn this for us, we’d be so happy!
覚えてくれたら 嬉しいな
I call myself Jupiter!
わたし木星が紹介しました！
It’s our pride; we’re best pals!
自慢だよ 最高の仲間っ
Surely it does not change what there was:
きっと 何があったって変わらない
The strong bond we feel,
強い絆を 感じてる
and everything we believe.
ずっと みんなを信じてる！